https://familyskitrips.com/privacy-policy/

Who we are
Our website address is: https://familyskitrips.com.
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for familyskitrips.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website.
• We collect NO private personal identifiable information from anyone that simply visits our site.
• We share no private information with anyone else.
• The only way we can collect private information from you is if you email us, post a comment or voluntarily sign up for our eNewsletter.
• If you see any factual errors on this web site please email the web site developer and include the page and factual information that you believe should be addresses.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
If you email us or post a comment, we are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email, comment form or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to get additional information from one of our lodging partners or information on Maine.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. Every broadcast email we send as a clear and safe “unsubscribe now” link at the bottom. If you receive a broadcast email from us simply click on the “unsubscribe now” link at the bottom of the email and you will be automatically removed from our email list permanently.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 207-967-6446 or via email us.
More Details on personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
We do NOT have any contact forms on this site.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
